getaroom.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Hotels - Cheap Hotel Rates - Rooms & Reservations

### GETAROOM PRIVACY POLICY

We respect your privacy. We will not provide your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your permission.

We send you information you want. You may choose whether and to what extent you receive marketing messages from Getaroom. Once you are registered, you can click on “My Reservations” and select the “Email” tab where you have a choice to opt in or out at any time to receive the following: email newsletters, email promotions, and email deals. If you are receiving the stated emails above and decide you no longer wish to receive this or any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on your “My Reservations” tab. It clearly shows you how to uncheck any boxes you may have checked prior and will update your preferences after you click the save button.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional email communications, you may opt out of receiving them by going to your “My Reservations” Tab or by emailing us at [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com) or by calling Customer Care at 800-HOTELS-8 (800-468-3578).

Also, you will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

We secure your data. We carefully monitor for intrusion attempts 24 hours a day, 7 days a week; deploy encryption technology, firewalls and advanced monitoring systems for your protection.

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell, rent, loan or disclose your personal information collected at this site to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent via email. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we collect, use and protect your personal information.

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain [www.getaroom.com](http://www.getaroom.com/) (the “Site”). By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access our Site.

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you, as part of the normal operation of our services, and what may happen to that information. Because we believe you should know as much as possible about Getaroom’s practices, we have prepared a detailed policy so that you can make informed decisions.

### Important Information.

Getaroom has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.getaroom.com](http://www.getaroom.com/). TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact Customer Care at [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com) or call Customer Care at 800-HOTELS-8 (800-468-3578). If you are not satisfied with our response [you can contact TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

### Information We Collect.

We collect two kinds of information about our online visitors, personal and non personal information. This personal information: User name, email address, and physical address, including City and State. Non personal information: shopping preferences, product searches, merchant searches, and general demographics. Our primary purpose in collecting personal and non personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. Cookies are small data files that are stored on an Internet user’s computer by a web server. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie.” The most important use of cookies is to help identify you while you are logged in to the Site, so we use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. If your browser does not accept log in cookies, you may be unable to use our Site. You will, however, be able to browse the Site. The information Getaroom collects from cookies and web server logs is used to improve our services to you and customize information you receive when visiting our site. We may also use and share information from cookies and web logs to analyze and improve our offerings. This information does not identify individual visitors or customers.

We also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes the Internet protocol addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/ time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to review trends, to administer our website, to track users’ movements around the web site and to gather demographic information about our customers. Most other web sites also gather this same information.

Certain third parties who host portions of our web site, and certain advertisers and others employ cookies and/or small pieces of code known as “pixel tags” that count users that have visited a page that contains these pixel tags without revealing any personal information. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. We use pixel tags to help us better manage content on the Site and to determine which content is effective. In addition, third-party advertisers and others may use pixel tags to help us track the effectiveness of our advertisements placed on third-party websites. Pixel tags on the Site are not used to collect personal information about our customers. We also use pixel tags in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. If you would like to opt out of these emails, please unsubscribe at the bottom of the email.

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, also use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.  Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:

[**http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118**](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [ Here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.  
If you have chosen to receive marketing messages from us about our products and services, we may use information from our log files, cookies or pixel tags to help us make those communications more useful to you.

We also get information from your transactions with us, our affiliates or non affiliated third parties such as account activity and your purchase information. We also use information from third parties, including public information, such as verification services and consumer reporting agencies (to comply with regulatory requirements, ensure the accurate data and prevent fraud, for example), or from other sources. We use this information to develop, offer and deliver our products and services, to process transactions in your accounts, and to obey legal and regulatory requirements. We limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum we require to deliver great service to our customers (including telling our customers about our hotel reservation services, deals, and other opportunities through email) and to run our business.

### Our Use of Your Information.

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to measure interest in the third-party products and services we offer; inform you via email about special offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions of the Site’s use. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple Customer IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use with your permission via the “My Reservations” tab, your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product and services offerings of Getaroom or third parties, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By opting in to receive this communication on the “My Reservations” tab of our Web Site, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications under the notification preferences on the “My Reservations” tab of our Web Site. You may make changes to your notification preferences on the “My Reservations” tab at any time or you may contact a customer service representative at [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com). We reserve the right to send you specific administrative notices that are required by law, regulation or as needed to service your account.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent, loan or disclose any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent via email notification. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide you with the ability to order the third-party products and services offered through the Site.

Advertisers. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address and password are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent.

We collect booking information via our forms that include the collection of personal and financial information. Some of these transaction pages may not appear on [www.getaroom.com](http://www.getaroom.com/) pages. However, we do control the privacy of the information given on these pages. Once the user submits the info, payment is made and verified, the booking is confirmed and removed from our inventory and passed on to the third party vendor booking the travel. The booking info then gets passed along to the third party for fulfillment. We do collect payment and verify credit card info to complete the booking, but we act only as the booking agent. The third party will receive the confirmation request from the guest for the reservation and then their privacy policy would be in effect. We do not have any control over the third party use of information or their privacy policies. [www.getaroom.com](http://www.getaroom.com/) is disclosing this information to users so that they have the option to not do business on the site. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to book with such lodging establishments. We may occasionally share information with our service providers that is in aggregate form. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information as it is in aggregate form and used to develop products that may be of interest to our customers. We may from time to time contract with third parties to handle surveys on the site. Upon completion of these projects, all information is returned to us. These companies that act as our service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

Legal Requests. Getaroom cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and our other customers from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address and Customer ID history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or report suspected illegal activity. If ConsumerClub is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### Blog/Forum.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at[customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com)_.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Testimonials.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com).

### Control of Your Customer ID and Password.

You are responsible for all actions taken with your Customer ID and password. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your Customer ID or password to any third parties. If you choose to share your Customer ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and, therefore, you should review that third party’s privacy policy. If you lose control of your Customer ID or password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your Customer ID or password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your Customer ID or password as detailed below.

### Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information.

We offer you the ability to automatically review and change or delete the information you submit to us by logging into the Site and entering in the new information yourself. Generally, we will not modify your personal information based on your request because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. You can change or delete your Customer ID, password, email address, contact information, user preferences and other information by going to the preferences and setup section in the user profile section of the site. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate.

Upon your request, we will deactivate your account, contact information and all other information from our active databases. To make this request, email [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com). Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

We will retain in our files some personal information you have requested to remove to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our agreements with you and comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will only be available to select Getaroom personnel.

### Other Information Collectors.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. This Site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that Getaroom is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are third-party providers of products or services, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Getaroom does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Social Media Widgets.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Google+ [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### A Special Note About Children.

Getaroom adheres to the federal privacy protection standards articulated in the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Getaroom takes children’s privacy seriously. Getaroom does not seek to collect personal information about children through the Site. Getaroom does not condition a child’s participation in an activity on the disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. If we become aware that a person submitting personal information to us through any part of our Site is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties. Since we do not seek to collect any personal information about children, and we delete any information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and deleted the information, then we will of course honor that request.

### Security.

Your information is stored on Getaroom’s servers located in the United States. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including monitoring for intrusion attempts, encryption technology, “firewalls,” Secure Socket Layers and security audits and inspections. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. When setting up an account, your information is stored behind a secure server via multiple encryption methods as well as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) on the site. Information stored on the server is only available to a select number of people at Getaroom that have access to these records. We encourage the use of encryption to communicate with Getaroom. The privacy of communication over the Internet cannot be guaranteed because the Internet is not a secure medium. Getaroom does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss or damage you my experience or incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the Internet by or to Getaroom. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to [customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com).

Please remember that you also play a valuable part in data security. You should never share your Getaroom customer id or password with anyone. If you feel any of your information has been compromised, you should change it immediately. After you have finished using our site, you should log out of your Getaroom account and exit your browser so that no unauthorized persons can use our site under your name and account information.

### Notification of Changes.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy when you visit the Site to review the current policy. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. Getaroom will use the information collected on the Site in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage prior to the change becoming effective.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit Getaroom’s [Terms of Use](http://news.getaroom.com/terms-of-use/) for terms governing the use of the entire Site.

Thank you for being our customer.

This privacy statement covers the site [http://www.getaroom.com](http://www.getaroom.com/) . If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy contact Customer Care at[customerservice@getaroom.com](mailto:customerservice@getaroom.com) or call Customer Care at 800-HOTELS-8 (800-468-3578).

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 06/02/14

Getaroom, Inc. 3010 LBJ Freeway Suite 1550 Dallas, Texas, 75234
